mysale.my 2014-04-26

# Mysale.my - Privacy

## Privacy Policy

MYSALE.MY, referred to below as MySale, is an online retailer of consumer goods owned and operated by Ozsale Pty Limited (ABN 11 118 610 987) (“Ozsale”), a company registered in Australia.

MySale values our relationship with you and the other users of this website. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of your personally identifiable information that we may collect when you use the Website. Accordingly, we have implemented this Privacy Policy to inform you of the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via our contact us page, e-mail us contactus@mysale.my or call 03 7391 7967.

If you wish to unsubscribe from our daily notifications you can do so by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our email notifications or by visiting www.mysale.my/unsubscribe.aspx.

Mysale is located at Lot G.03, Wisma Academy, 4A Jalan 19/1, 46300 Petaling Jaya Selangor

## MYSALE's Commitment to Online Security

Your personal information is treated with the greatest of care. Sensitive payment information such as credit card details is NEVER stored on the Internet with our system.

How Your Information May Be Shared

We never sell or rent your personal information. MySale generally does not share your personal information with others unless this is necessary for the purposes for which you gave it to us but there may be times when we need to disclose your personal information. MySale may release personal information under the following circumstances and/or to the following parties:

  * Where release is required or authorised by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation or is requested by a law enforcement agency or emergency services;
  * Where our records indicate a company or an individual may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of;
  * To appropriate persons, where your communication suggests possible harm to others.
  * To our related companies (some of which are based outside of Malaysia) who may use and disclose your information for the same or similar purposes as us.
  * To facilitate the sale or other disposition of our business.
  * For carrying out marketing and products analysis and marketing MySale and MySale related companies’ products and services.

## Member’s Right to Access and Correct Personal Information

You have right to access and correct your personal information held by us about you, if we hold that information in a way that it can be readily retrieved. You can access and correct your personal information under “My Account”. Alternatively you can send us an email via our “My Contacts” page.

## Invite a friend

MySale provides facilities throughout the site to refer friends to MySale. You may not use the "Invite a friend" service or other email forwarding services that we offer to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our privacy policy or Terms and Conditions. We do not permanently store, sell, or rent these email messages or the email addresses.

## Membership Registration

Our site's registration form requires you to provide us contact information and may also require demographic information. We may use your contact information from the registration form to send you information about our company. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary.

## Passwords

You are responsible for all actions taken with your user name, email address and password. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your MySale password to any third parties. If you choose to share your user name, email address and password or your information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with this information and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy.

## Security

Transactions are processed via an industry standard secure https connection using Citicorp Payment Services Inc. as a third party payment gateway. This means that you can be assured that your sensitive data such as credit card numbers will remain confidential because all information is 128bit encrypted. The server we connect to is authenticated through PKI certificates issued by a root Certificate Authority. Our payment page is also fully PCI DSS compliant please visit <https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/tech/> for more information.

## Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in a browser-related file on your computer's hard drive when you use our Website. We use cookies to improve the member experience. We also use them to deliver information and fresh content specific to your interests. Cookies are widely used on most major Web sites. Citicorp Payment Services Inc.  
MySale mostly uses "session" cookies, which are removed from your computer once you leave MySale. These are used so our service can remember that you have logged in already and prevent you doing so more frequently. The technology we use (Microsoft .NET), requires the use of session cookies. Session cookies expire and are deleted after 30 minutes of no activity on MySale.  
MySale also uses persistent cookies to personalise the user experience, to help protect our members and to provide us with research information (such as how often members visit MySale each month). Persistent cookies allow us to track users on MySale and help us identify users abusing the MySale service.

## Membership Removal

If you wish to be removed from our database for any reason, simply send us an email requesting to be removed via our “My Contact” page.

## Updates to our information practices

MySale reserves the right to add to, delete or change these terms because of frequent changes in Internet technology and applicable law. As such, you should check this privacy policy from time to time for such changes.
